ai.Boss_Warning
Enemies Attack
ai.205001_Ge_Leimu
Team dungeons require cohesion between teams. Collect buffs from the ground to increase your combat power!
ai.205002_Storm
Blizzard has a powerful slow effect! Careful!
ai.205003_Fire
The lava throughout this level will deal ongoing damage. Be sure to stay away!
ai.205004_Laser
You'll be paralyzed if you touch the laser. Avoid it!
ai.205005_Rain
Poisonous Rains deal ongoing damage. Use the healing items on this level wisely!
ai.205006_Recovery
The shining areas across levels heal monster HP!
ai.205007_Daboluo
Diabolos has incredibly high attack! Make use of items throughout the level to defeat it!
ai.205008_xuenu
Enemies have a strong protective barrier. Before it is destroyed, it will absorb most damage.
ai.205009_BaneRain
The Poisonous Rain deals ongoing damage. Remember to heal yourself!
ai.205002_Ge_Leimujineng
When you summon Golem, an ancient totem with an invincibility effect appears. Break the totem quickly!
ai.108_ruodianzhiyin
Weak point discovered! Hit the weak point to deal tons of damage!
ai.dangerous_warning
Alert! The enemy is about to use a devastating blow!
ai.4152_bulaikeben
Note: Enemies will use powerful skills!
ai.406shengcuntishi
Flexible positioning and use of healing skills will increase your heroes' survival in battle. Hang on to the end!
ai.203shouhushuijing
Warning! The crystal is under attack!
ai.jishajijia
The magitek armor is activating. Destroy it quickly!
ai.daliangbuding
Careful, many monsters are coming!
ai.dabuding
A giant monster is coming! Protect the crystal!
ai.chanajineng
Caetuna has powerful restorative and control powers
teamemoticons.run
Run!
teamemoticons.pei
Ignore
teamemoticons.hello
Greet
teamemoticons.wizard
Amazing
ai.anduoliya
Attention! Protect Queen Andoria!
ai.qingrenjie1
Attention! Defeat the Demon Flower within a limited time to save Queen Andoria!
ai.qingrenjie2
Attention! The gate leading the way ahead is opened. Quickly, go to save Queen Andoria!
ai.qingrenjie3
Come close to Queen Andoria and you will be healed!
ai.zhenlongxingji
Alarm! Don't let young dragons from get close to Claes
ai.antela2
Activate the mechanism in the center to stop the meteor
ai.xingjidazhao
Watch out for thunderclaps!
ai.nvshengjie
Protect Ameena from being damaged
ai.tianqi
The lightning device is ready, please go into the center to trigger it!
ai.tianqi2
Attention! Lightning devices in the center of the battlefield can help!
ai.yurenjie1
Time for Happy Cards!
ai.yurenjie2
Use the magic card and have some fun!
ai.yichuan
Attention! The stage required manual operation!
ai.chuanshanjia
The enemy can reflect damage now. Stop the attack!
