bountymission_1_name
Demon Shadow
bountymission_1_descript
None are willing to provoke the demonic magic manipulators. They are powerful and cunning, and show no mercy. When fighting them, even prayer is superfluous.
bountymission_2_name
Demon Shadow
bountymission_2_descript
None are willing to provoke the demonic magic manipulators. They are powerful and cunning, and show no mercy. When fighting them, even prayer is superfluous.
bountymission_3_name
Demon Shadow
bountymission_3_descript
None are willing to provoke the demonic magic manipulators. They are powerful and cunning, and show no mercy. When fighting them, even prayer is superfluous.
bountymission_4_name
Demon Shadow
bountymission_4_descript
None are willing to provoke the demonic magic manipulators. They are powerful and cunning, and show no mercy. When fighting them, even prayer is superfluous.
bountymission_5_name
Demon Shadow
bountymission_5_descript
None are willing to provoke the demonic magic manipulators. They are powerful and cunning, and show no mercy. When fighting them, even prayer is superfluous.
bountymission_6_name
Dark Emissary
bountymission_6_descript
Their power that spreads from the abyss, bringing with it a primitive and dark fear. Here, your purpose is to survive.
bountymission_7_name
Dark Emissary
bountymission_7_descript
Their power that spreads from the abyss, bringing with it a primitive and dark fear. Here, your purpose is to survive.
bountymission_8_name
Dark Emissary
bountymission_8_descript
Their power that spreads from the abyss, bringing with it a primitive and dark fear. Here, your purpose is to survive.
bountymission_9_name
Dark Emissary
bountymission_9_descript
Their power that spreads from the abyss, bringing with it a primitive and dark fear. Here, your purpose is to survive.
bountymission_10_name
Dark Emissary
bountymission_10_descript
Their power that spreads from the abyss, bringing with it a primitive and dark fear. Here, your purpose is to overcome it - to live.
bountymission_11_name
Icy Test
bountymission_11_descript
Angels of frost are heralds of winter. They use snow, the purest substance in the world, to cause pain!
bountymission_12_name
Icy Test
bountymission_12_descript
Angels of frost are heralds of winter. They use snow, the purest substance in the world, to cause pain!
bountymission_13_name
Icy Test
bountymission_13_descript
Angels of frost are heralds of winter. They use snow, the purest substance in the world, to cause pain!
bountymission_14_name
Icy Test
bountymission_14_descript
Angels of frost are heralds of winter. They use snow, the purest substance in the world, to cause pain!
bountymission_15_name
Icy Test
bountymission_15_descript
Angels of frost are heralds of winter. They use snow, the purest substance in the world, to cause pain!
bountymission_16_name
Burning Ambition
bountymission_16_descript
They have an overwhelming desire to burn everything! To dampen this flame, you'll need to be more hot-blooded then they!
bountymission_17_name
Burning Ambition
bountymission_17_descript
They have an overwhelming desire to burn everything! To dampen this flame, you'll need to be more hot-blooded then they!
bountymission_18_name
Burning Ambition
bountymission_18_descript
They have an overwhelming desire to burn everything! To dampen this flame, you'll need to be more hot-blooded then they!
bountymission_19_name
Burning Ambition
bountymission_19_descript
They have an overwhelming desire to burn everything! To dampen this flame, you'll need to be more hot-blooded then they!
bountymission_20_name
Burning Ambition
bountymission_20_descript
They have an overwhelming desire to burn everything! To dampen this flame, you'll need to be more hot-blooded then they!
bountymission_21_name
Thundering Battlefield
bountymission_21_descript
Created in a bang and ending with a whisper. Thunder magic users have extremely powerful destructive abilities. It is not easy to challenge them.
bountymission_22_name
Thundering Battlefield
bountymission_22_descript
Created in a bang and ending with a whisper. Thunder magic users have extremely powerful destructive abilities. It is not easy to challenge them.
bountymission_23_name
Thundering Battlefield
bountymission_23_descript
Created in a bang and ending with a whisper. Thunder magic users have extremely powerful destructive abilities. It is not easy to challenge them.
bountymission_24_name
Thundering Battlefield
bountymission_24_descript
Created in a bang and ending with a whisper. Thunder magic users have extremely powerful destructive abilities. It is not easy to challenge them.
bountymission_25_name
Thundering Battlefield
bountymission_25_descript
Created in a bang and ending with a whisper. Thunder magic users have extremely powerful destructive abilities. It is not easy to challenge them.
bountymission_26_name
Nature's Power
bountymission_26_descript
Once you realize you've entered a Nature trap, it's already too late! They are gentle, but extremely dangerous
bountymission_27_name
Nature's Power
bountymission_27_descript
Once you realize you've entered a Nature trap, it's already too late! They are gentle, but extremely dangerous
bountymission_28_name
Nature's Power
bountymission_28_descript
Once you realize you've entered a Nature trap, it's already too late! They are gentle, but extremely dangerous
bountymission_29_name
Nature's Power
bountymission_29_descript
Once you realize you've entered a Nature trap, it's already too late! They are gentle, but extremely dangerous
bountymission_30_name
Nature's Power
bountymission_30_descript
Once you realize you've entered a Nature trap, it's already too late! They are gentle, but extremely dangerous
