groups_1_des
[u]Account and Log in Issues
groups_1_title
About account
groups_1_q1
[E89D44]Q: How to switch accounts? [-]
groups_1_a1
A: In the logging page: 【Switch Account】-【Logout】; Or in the game, tap the head portrait-【Logout】, then you can log in another account.
groups_1_q2
[E89D44]Q: Which type is my account?[-]
groups_1_a2
A: There are 3 account types. The first is PlayNow Account. The second is third party account, such as Google+/Facebook/Twitter. The third is Efun account, containing username and password.
groups_1_q3
[E89D44]Q: Forget password? [-]
groups_1_a3
A: You can find back password of Efun account with email: 【Login】-【Account Setting】-【Forget Password】
groups_1_q4
[E89D44]Q: I need help...[-]
groups_1_a4
A: Please contact our CS through Facebook: www.facebook.com/efunidff/
groups_2_des
[u]Purchase Issues
groups_2_title
Recharges
groups_2_q1
[E89D44]Q: How to recharge?[-]
groups_2_a1
A: You can tap the button 【Recharge】 in the game with iTunes or GoogleWallet. For more information, please contact our CS through facebook.
groups_2_q2
[E89D44]Q: What if I haven’t received diamonds, but my money has been deducted?[-]
groups_2_a2
A: Please contact our CS through Facebook, as well as your account and recharge information in details.\n\nOur official Facebook: www.facebook.com/efunidff/
groups_3_des
[u]Game Control Issues
groups_3_title
Operations
groups_3_q1
[E89D44]Q: How to swap the locations of heroes in my part formation? [-]
groups_3_a1
A: Tap the replace hero button in the party interface. After de-selecting the “only display idle heroes” you can select the hero to replace. Main characters cannot be swapped.
groups_3_q2
[E89D44]Q: Can I recover incorrectly made Rank Up, Dissolves, Crafts, or Transformations? [-]
groups_3_a2
A: You cannot recover it. Please be careful!
groups_3_q3
[E89D44]Q: How to use Invitation codes? [-]
groups_3_a3
A: The inviting player sends their code to the invited player. After the invited player enters the game, they can enter the code within the “Recommended Binding” section of Benefits to bind the inviting player.
groups_3_q4
[E89D44]Q: How to delete recent contacts in my chat? [-]
groups_3_a4
A: On the right side of the chat box are the delete and report chat buttons. You can delete contacts or report others.
groups_3_q5
[E89D44]Q: What can I do if someone is sending inappropriate messages or ads in the public chat channel? [-]
groups_3_a5
A: Tap the player’s icon to chat. You can find the report button in the chat interface.
groups_4_des
[u]Gameplay Issues
groups_4_title
About game-play
groups_4_q1
[E89D44]Q: My Accessory Backpack is full. Can I sell Accessories? [-]
groups_4_a1
A: Accessory Enhancement allows you to devour useless Accessories. You can select extra accessories to act as experience for accessory enhancement.
groups_4_q2
[E89D44]Q: How to awaken a Hero? [-]
groups_4_a2
A: Hero doesn’t have destiny and bonded hero not awakened.
groups_4_q3
[E89D44]Q: How to help friends in the Hero Trials? [-]
groups_4_a3
A: Friend assistance requests will appear in the main interface. You can also enter the Hero Trial interface and tap the friend support info on the right.
groups_4_q4
[E89D44]Q: How to get Hero Potential? [-]
groups_4_a4
A: Increase Awakening Level after getting a new hero to increase all Potential points.
groups_4_q5
[E89D44]Q: Are the previous clears of daily target event missions not counted? [-]
groups_4_a5
A: Only mission completions during event are counted.
groups_4_q6
[E89D44]Q: Amounts of rewards claimed from World Boss are different[-]
groups_4_a6
A: The amount of time a player can claim World Boss rewards is dependent on player level. Higher level players can claim rewards more times.
groups_4_q7
[E89D44]Q: Where are the Artifacts drawn from the lottery? [-]
groups_4_a7
A: Artifacts can be seen after Lv. 65. At that time you’ll be able to see Gear Vault - Artifacts in the bottom of the screen.
groups_5_des
[u]Guild Issues
groups_5_title
Guild Related
groups_5_q1
[E89D44]Q: How to create a Guild? [-]
groups_5_a1
A: Reach VIP2 or Lv.30 to create a Guild.
groups_5_q2
[E89D44]Q: After leaving one Guild, how long do I need to join another one? [-]
groups_5_a2
A: You must wait 8 hours after leaving to join another Guild.
groups_5_q3
[E89D44]Q: How to leave a Guild? [-]
groups_5_a3
A: Enter the Guild Hall within the Guild interface to exit the Guild.
groups_5_q4
[E89D44]Q: What can I do if the Guild Leader isn’t online for a long time? [-]
groups_5_a4
A: If the Guild Leader doesn’t log in for 3 days, authority will be automatically handed over to the Vice Leader or player that contributed the most Activity.
groups_5_q5
[E89D44]Q: Why does a guild member show up as “not present” in the Guild Hire menu? [-]
groups_5_a5
A: Within the Guild’s Mercenary section, tap join to be hired by another and get benefits.
groups_5_q6
[E89D44]Q: How does the Guild Leader leave the Guild? [-]
groups_5_a6
A: The Guild Leader will need to hand over his position to another member before leaving the guild. They can also leave if they’re the only member of the Guild.
