sharetasks_80001_loc
Leveled up again. I'm Level 30 now in the "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING" mobile game! Hurry and join us!
sharetasks_80002_loc
Leveled up again. I'm Level 50 now in the "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING" mobile game! Hurry and join us!
sharetasks_80003_loc
Leveled up again. I'm Level 60 now in the "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING" mobile game! Hurry and join us!
sharetasks_80004_loc
Leveled up again. I'm Level 70 now in the "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING" mobile game! Hurry and join us!
sharetasks_80005_loc
Leveled up again. I'm Level 80 now in the "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING" mobile game! Hurry and join us!
sharetasks_80006_loc
Leveled up again. I'm Level 90 now in the "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING" mobile game! Hurry and join us!
sharetasks_80007_loc
Leveled up again. I'm Level 100 now in the "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING" mobile game! Hurry and join us!
sharetasks_81001_loc
Fighting with Judge, defeating armored Bosses, my combat power has reached a million in Final Fantasy Awakening. Revisit where the dream first began. Everything is here!
sharetasks_81002_loc
Fighting with Judge, defeating armored Bosses, my combat power has reached 10 million in Final Fantasy Awakening. Revisit where the dream first began. Everything is here!
sharetasks_82001_loc
Is there anyone worth challenging? I have defeated all competitors in "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING",  ranking top 500 in the arena! Are you too scared to challenge me?
sharetasks_82002_loc
Is there anyone worth challenging? I have defeated all competitors in "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING",  ranking top 500 in the arena! Are you too scared to challenge me?
sharetasks_82003_loc
Is there anyone worth challenging? I have defeated all competitors in "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING",  ranking top 500 in the arena! Are you too scared to challenge me?
sharetasks_82004_loc
Is there anyone worth challenging? I have defeated all competitors in "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING",  ranking top 500 in the arena! Are you too scared to challenge me?
sharetasks_82005_loc
Is there anyone worth challenging? I have defeated all competitors in "FINAL FANTASY AWAKENING",  ranking top 500 in the arena! Are you too scared to challenge me?
