ui.heroshift.not.enough.cost
Insufficient currency,  cannot convert hero
ui.heroshift.introduction
Only Legendary heroes can be transformed into another hero of the same quality by Rebirth \nThe transfer price is related to Hero quality and Hero Rank \nThe higher quality hero to be transferred,  the higher price required for conversion. The Quality, Rank and EXP will be succeded after transformation. \n The skill break level becomes the initial state and Breakthrough materials will all be returned
ui.hero.shift.title
Soul Transfer
ui.hero.shift.no.oraginhero
There are no available Heroes
ui.hero.shift.self.herolist
Please choose your own hero
ui.hero.shift.optional.herolist
Please choose the hero to be transformed into
ui.heroshift.main.text
Transformed Hero will inherit the original hero level and rank. gold consumed during skills breakthrough will be returned
